我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help
我秘密地打击犯罪
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back,
才把我救回来  但我们的世界
and in doing so our world
也因此出现了新的威胁
was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash."
12个标记  12个超能力者
12 markers, 12 metas.
你的身体退化太快
Your body's deteriorating faster
椅子会承受不住
than the chair can handle.
我不只占据了多米尼克的身体
I didn't just take Dominic's body.
还拥有了他的能力
I took his ability.
希尔伯特·伦丁  他可以把物体压缩
Sylbert Rundine can shrink objects and return them
也可以让他们变回原来大小
to original size.
迪肯  控制科技
Deacon-- controls technology.
贝琪·夏普可以操控运气
Becky Sharpe can manipulate luck.
没有东西阻止他进入超能力片区中
There's nothing keeping him from going in the meta wing
吸收铁山监狱里每个超能力者的超能力
and absorbing the powers.
你应当想变成谁就能变成谁才对
You should be able to change into anyone you can think of.
现在如何
How's this?
我想你在找我
I believe you are looking for me.
是拉尔夫
It's Ralph.
巴里·艾伦即刻释放
Barry Allen is hereby released immediately.
他只想要公交车上的超能力者
He only wants the bus metas.
他想要他们的超能力
He wants their powers.
为什么都像看死人那样看着我
Why is everyone looking at me like I'm a dead man?
爱蒂  发生什么了
Addie, hey, what's going on?
你应该和凯特谈谈
I think you should talk to Kat.
谈什么
About what?
你就去见他吧  艾伦
Just go see him, Allen.
好吧
Okay.
容忍先前的行政行为
Tolerate the behavior that the previous administration
爱蒂说你想见我
Addie said you wanted to see me.
对  关门
Yeah, shut the door.
我向你们承诺  我们会铲除一切层面的腐败
I promise you we will root out all corruption
爆炸性新闻
格里高利·沃夫  铁山监狱监狱长  英勇牺牲
重建你们对公务员的信心
at all levels and restore your faith in public servants.
范布伦之名永远
The name Van Buren is a name that has always
代表廉洁
stood for integrity.
我也许是市长
I may be the Mayor--
我们有个我不知道怎么解决的问题
We've got a problem that I'm not sure how to fix.
有些人觉得你不应该回到警局
Some people don't think you should be back on the force.
因为迪沃
Because of DeVoe?
我的一切指控都洗清了
I was cleared of all charges.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
他还活着
He's alive.
而且他很合作
I know, and he's been cooperating,
乖乖进来  回答问题
coming in, answering questions.
那问题是什么
So what's the problem?
现在的人什么都不相信
People nowadays will believe anything.
虚假新闻  社交媒体
Fake news, social media.
指控被视为事实
Allegations are treated as facts.
但是迪沃还活着
But DeVoe being alive?
在你上诉听证的时候出现在法庭
Showing up in the courtroom at your appeal hearing?
中城的一些人并不相信那真的是他
Some people in Central City don't buy it's actually him.
那他们觉得那是什么
Well, who do they think it was?
鬼知道
Who the hell knows?
但我们生活在一个超能力者遍布的城市
But we live in a city full of meta-humans.
这里是阴谋论者的天堂
It's a conspiracy theorist's dream.
这意味着什么
So, what does this mean?
你要  你要开了我
Are you--you firing me?
不是开除
Not firing.
但是我被要求  下令让你
But I have been asked to request that you take
请一段时间假
a leave of absence.
谁要求的
By whom?
大家都觉着这样好点
Thinks it'll be easier for everyone.
更容易重建公众的信心和其他的
Restoring the faith and all that.
请多久
For how long?
期限不定
Indefinitely.
巴里
Look, Barry,
如果你想让我为此斗争
if you want me to fight this thing,
我会尽我所能
I'll do what I can.
但是这个新市长  自从贝罗斯丑闻后
But this new Mayor, she's got a lot to prove
她要证明一堆东西
since the Bellows debacle.
你觉得我什么时候能回来
When do you think I can come back?
所有人都相信迪沃真的活蹦乱跳的时候
When everyone believes DeVoe is really alive and well.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十四集
这不是永久的  是吗
It's not permanent, is it?
他说这是不定期的
I mean, he said it was indefinite.
如果是为你好的话
They wouldn't have given you your ID back
他们不会马上把你的身份卡给你
if it was for good.
也许这是最好的  巴里
I mean, maybe this is for the best, Barry.
你得证明迪沃还活着
I mean, you need to prove that DeVoe is still alive.
你现在可以作为闪电侠做这件事
And you can do that now as The Flash.
也许
Yeah, maybe.
顺便  我们和他的事有什么进展吗
How are we doing with him, by the way?
我们还有四个公交车上的超能力者没找到
We know that we still have four bus metas left to find.
迪沃已经吸收了基尔戈  凶险星
And that DeVoe has absorbed the powers of Kilgore,
受害者
布莱克·柏森  头脑风暴  矮星的能力
Hazard, Black Bison, Brainstorm, and Dwarfstar.
辐射和特蕾西在一起  安全
Fallout is safe with Tracy.
但哭泣者失去踪迹有一段时间了
But the Weeper is M.I.A.
迪沃肯定抓住他了
Then DeVoe must have him.
现在就剩拉尔夫了
Well, that just leaves Ralph.
拉尔夫和我们在一起是安全的
Ralph is safe with us.
但其他四个超能力者并不安全
But the other four metas aren't.
迪沃绝对会杀了他们然后取得他们的力量
DeVoe will absolutely kill them and take their powers.
他为什么需要他们的力量
But why does he need their powers?
我猜不出他想干什么
I can't figure out his end game.
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只知道最后四个超能力者是关键
I just know that these last four metas are the key.
这就是为何我们要找到他们
That's why we need to find them.
而且我们必将找到他们
And find them we will.
你们去哪儿了
Where have you guys been?
去了我小小的家外之家
A little home away from home,
别名公共汽车站
otherwise known as the bus depot.
但是我给西斯科展示了一个我从
But I showed Cisco here an old P.I. Trick
我导师哥伦布那儿学来的老式侦探技巧
I learned from my mentor, Columbo.
那辆装超能力者的405路公交的失物招领盒
Lost and found box from meta bus 405.
一个针对所有人的提问  我怎么沦落到
Question for the room, how did I get stuck
和拉尔夫两人一组的境地来的
doing the buddy system thing with Ralph?
这是保证拉尔夫安全的最佳方式  西斯科
It's the best way to keep Ralph safe, Cisco.
对  保证拉尔夫安全的最佳方式  西斯科
Yeah, it's the best way to keep Ralph safe, Cisco.
显然你们从没有被迫在一个
Well, clearly you've never had to stay over
用啤酒标志的霓虹灯当台灯
at an apartment that uses neon beer signs for lamps
用厨房水槽当淋浴器的公寓过过夜
and the kitchen sink for a shower.
拉尔夫  我爱你
Ralph, I love you.
但你居然睡蒲团上
But you sleep on a futon.
蒲团没那么糟
Futon's not that bad.
湿掉的时候就是那么糟
It is when it's damp.
它为什么湿了
Why is it damp?
我睡觉的时候出很多汗
I sweat a lot when I sleep.
你真恶心
You nasty.
我的牙齿固位器
Oh, hey, my retainer.
我找这个很久了
Been looking for this.
牙齿固位器
Retainer.
你证明了你的论点
Okay, you made your point.
虽然这点不需要证明
Not that the point needed to be made.
我来接下一班
I'll take the next shift.
你是个好人  巴里·艾伦
You're a good man, Barry Allen.
认真的  这年头谁还用CD啊
Really? Who uses CDs anymore?
伊兹·鲍温
声轨样本
一个企图交好运的音乐家
A musician trying to catch their break.
伊兹·鲍温  声轨样本
Izzy Bowin.
乡村音乐
Ugh, country.
音乐五音不全的干儿子
Music's tone deaf stepchild.
有人记得车上有带小提琴的人吗
All right, remember anyone on the bus with a fiddle?
有个戴牛仔帽的人
There was a guy with a cowboy hat on
坐我后面  也许是他
sitting behind me. Maybe it was him.
男孩  我相信我们总能找出来的
Boy, I sure wish we had a way of finding out.
伊兹·鲍温
Izzy Bowin.
爆裂马鞍沙龙
伊兹  你愿意再测试一下麦克风吗
Izzy, you wanna give us one more mic check?
测试一下  测试  测试  一  二
Check one, check, check, one two.
是个女孩  不是男孩
Okay, well, it's a her, not a him.
她在爆裂马鞍驻唱
And she's playing a gig at the Busted Saddle.
拉尔夫  出发吧
All right. Ralph, let's go.
不  没门  我恨乡村音乐
No, no way. I hate country music.
二人一组  该我了  来吧
Well, buddy system. It's my turn. Come on.
你坚持的话
If you insist.
她唱得不错
She's good.
她进步了  但技巧不够圆润
She's improving, but she lacks refinement.
所以你一点都不被她惊艳
So you're not impressed by her at all?
我现在的面孔
The resting face of my current visage
或许比我过去的看着更愉快
may be more pleasant than the one I used to display.
但我向你保证  这决不是一个男人
But I assure you, this is not the look of a man
为音乐之美赞叹的表情
awed by symphonic greatness.
克利福德  克利福德
Clifford! Clifford!
这具身体  正在急速衰败
This body, it's deteriorating rapidly.
你系统中新超能力所带来的暗物质
The additional dark matter in your system
拖垮了宿主
from each of your new powers is wearing down your host.
它吸收太多新身体的能量
It's straining too much of this body's new energy.
那我必须换上下一具身体
Then I must move into the next one.
但你说伊兹·鲍温还没准备好
But you said that Izzy Bowen wasn't ready,
我们得再找一个
that we needed to find another.
我们没时间了
We don't have time.
我们必须马上行动
We must act now.
也许我们太迟了
We may be too late.
伊兹·鲍温
Izzy Bowin?
我是
That's me.
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen.
我是中城警局的...
I'm with CCP--
那是一个厂牌吗
Is that a label?
也许在另一个地球上
Maybe on another Earth.
你想要签名照还是电话号码之类的
Okay, well, you want an autograph or a phone number, something?
不是  不是要这些
Uh, no, no. Nothing like that.
好吧
Okay.
如果不是为了公事  也不是为了娱乐
Well, if it ain't business and it ain't pleasure,
那我们没什么好谈的  对吧
then we got nothing left to talk about, now do we?
下周再来一次
Do it again next week.
谢谢
Thank you.
干得好
Great work.
对不起  容我解释一下
Okay, I'm sorry. Let me explain.
有一个非常聪明  又很危险的人在找你
Someone very smart and very dangerous is coming after you.
我吗
Me?
没错
Yep.
看在上帝的份上
Okay, now, why in the name of God
为什么会有危险人物来找我
would anybody dangerous be coming after me?
因为你有超能力
Because you have powers.
四个月前
Four months ago,
你坐上了中城405路公车
you were on Central City bus 405.
那辆公车上充斥了暗物质
That bus got showered with dark matter
令车上所有的人都变成了超能力者
and made everyone on it a meta-human.
现在这件事的幕后黑手
Now the person responsible for doing that
想把那些超能力占为己有
wants those powers for themself.
让我猜猜
Okay, and let me guess.
你们俩是来保护我的
You boys are here to protect me.
差不多是这样吧
Something like that.
我们可以晚点再详细解释
Look, we can explain more later,
但是现在我们需要你跟我们走
but now we just need you to come with us.
不  没那个必要
Oh, no, that's not necessary.
我爸被人保释了  之后不久我妈也被保释了
My daddy bailed. Mama bailed not long after.
我一辈子都在照顾他人
And I have been looking out for myself my entire life.
但这次不一样
This time it's different.
你照顾不了自己  拜托
You can't. Please.
我们要走了
We need to go.
我是不会和你们任何一个人走的
I ain't going anywhere with either of you.
我认为你应该重新考虑一下
I think you should reconsider that.
我不在乎你们怎么想
I don't give a damn what you think.
看来我们现在知道她有什么超能力了
I guess now we know what her power is.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
-对  -对
- Yeah! - Yeah.
伊兹·鲍温
巴里耳膜
拉尔夫耳膜
你们俩很幸运
You two are lucky.
巴里  你的耳朵几乎恢复了
Barry, your ear is almost healed,
而德比  你的耳朵做了细胞拉伸
and Dibny, yours just stretched.
我的听力还是不太好
Well, I still can't hear all that great.
就当是因祸得福吧
Consider that a blessing in disguise.
未来能少听到一些鼻音
Less twang in your future.
再等一个小时就会好了
Give it an hour. You'll be fine.
所以伊兹·鲍温能控制音乐
So Izzy Bowin can control music.
不如说是声波
More like sound waves.
声波  好名字
Soundwave. That's a great name.
如果《变形金刚》里没先占用  那就好了
It would be, if it wasn't already taken by a Transformer.
看来那像是数十亿的微小碎片
Okay, well, it looks like billions of tiny shrapnel
-从这里撕裂开  -没错
- ripped through this. - Exactly.
声音只是数十亿微小气体分子
Sound is just the force of billions of tiny gas molecules
相互碰撞的力量
colliding into one another.
所以如果你能驾驭和增强动能
So if you can harness and amplify kinetic energy,
-你就能获得...  -分子碎片
- you get-- - Molecular shrapnel.
我们要继续追查
Okay, well, we gotta keep searching.
如果我们不能快点查到她的下落
If we can't track her down soon,
她就会落入迪沃的手中
she's gonna fall right into DeVoe's hands.
说到追查人的下落
Speaking of tracking people down,
哈里什么时候从地球二回来
when's Harry getting back from Earth Two?
塞西尔·霍尔顿地检官
DA Cecile Horton.
哈里  你好
Harry, hey.
你什么时候从你的地球回来的
When did you get back from your Earth?
刚回来的
Just got back.
自己给自己来点提神的东西
Getting myself a little pick me up.
我们一起  孩子
You and me both, kid.
-很高兴见到你  -嗯
- Okay, good talk. - Yeah.
其实我认为
Actually, you know, I don't think that, uh,
孕妇不应该摄入咖啡因
pregnant people are supposed to consume caffeine.
医生说一天喝一杯没事
Uh, yeah, doctor says one cup a day is fine.
只有上帝知道我需要咖啡因
And lord knows I need it.
你难以相信我需要咖啡的程度
I need it more than you could possibly imagine.
当然了  肯定非常累人
Apparently. Must be exhausting.
是的  他害得我一晚都不能睡
It is. He's keeping me up all night.
男孩吗  艾伦不是说你怀的是女孩吗
"He"? I thought Allen said you were having a girl.
我说的不是宝宝
Yeah, and I'm not talking about the baby.
我说的是乔
I'm talking about Joe.
乔害我睡不着
Joe is keeping me up.
不是  哈里  过来
No, Harry, come here.
我新发现的读心超能力
My newfound ability to hear people's thoughts.
-懂了  我以为  -我能听到
- Oh, see, I thought-- - Yeah, I can hear--
乔的想法  他睡觉的时候我也能听到
Joe, his thoughts-- I can hear them while he's asleep.
-一整晚  -你能读到他的梦
- All night long. - You hear his dreams.
没错  疯狂又迅速
Yep. And they are crazy and fast.
而且非常大声
And oh so very loud.
我就像是身处在动作片里一样  哈里
It is like living in the middle of an action movie, Harry.
我深爱乔·韦斯特
I love Joe West with all my heart,
但我要告诉你  我没法
but I am telling you, I just-- I can't--
我太累了
I'm so tired.
我受不了了
I can't take it anymore.
真是太惨了  塞西尔·霍尔顿地检官
Yeah, well, that sucks, DA Cecile Horton.
-是的  -好吧
- Yes, it does. - Okay.
其实我也许能做些东西
Actually, I might be able to build something
来帮助你
that can help you with that.
哈里  谢谢你
Oh, Harry, thank you.
卫星已经运行了一整天
Satellite's been running all day,
但是仍未接收到任何不规则声音变动
but it's still not picking up any irregular sound variances.
我在市里搜过了  都找不到她
I checked the city. I can't find her.
宝贝  你搜了整座城市了吗
Babe, you checked the whole city?
是的
Yeah.
我们要在迪沃之前找到她
Look, we have to find her before DeVoe.
她有性命危险
Her life's on the line.
她这周还有一场演出
She had another gig this week.
她不相信她会出城
I doubt she'd skip town.
德比私家侦探建议我们该怎么找她呢
How would Dibny P.I. suggest we find her?
既然你问了
Well, since you asked,
有人看过她的网站吗
has anyone checked her web site?
"Has anyone checked her web site?"
德比  我们当然看过她的网站了
Dibs, of course we've checked her web site.
没人看过她的网站吗
No one has checked her web site?
-爱瑞丝  -马上看
- Iris! - Yeah, I'm-- I'm on it.
现在就看
I'm looking now. Um...
巡演信息
帖子
各位  她还在城里
Guys, she's still in town.
刚刚完成下首新单的首演
"I just picked up the first run of my next single
爱死沙龙录音棚的天才们
and love the geniuses at Saloon Sounds."
拉尔夫  再来第二轮
All right, Ralph. Take two.
西斯科  我们也许需要震波的帮忙
Cisco, we might need Vibe's help.
整装待发
Giddy up.
快点走  我们赶时间
Come on, let's go. We're in a hurry.
伊兹·鲍温  我们需要你跟我们走
Izzy Bowin, we need you to come with us.
-闪电侠  -你现在有危险
- Flash? - You're in danger.
我知道  每个人都在和我说
I know, everybody keeps telling me that.
在你听进去之前  会一直有人和你说
And you're gonna keep hearing it until it sinks in.
你要相信我们
You just have to trust us.
我们不会伤害你的  但我们知道有人会
We're not gonna hurt you, but we know someone who will.
谁会伤害我
Who is going to hurt me?
我会
I am.
你们来就为了警告我小心她吗
Y'all came to warn me about her?
迪沃
DeVoe.
你好啊  闪电侠
Hello, Flash.
放过伊兹
You're gonna leave Izzy alone.
你真的没从我们过去的交手当中吸取教训
You know, you really don't learn from our past encounters,
是吗
do you?
你不够聪明  阻止不了我得到我想要的
You're not smart enough to stop me from getting what I want.
而我现在想要的就是她
And what I want now is her.
这是不可能的
That's not gonna happen.
现在是三人对一人  天才
It's three against one, genius.
算算这条数吧  震波
Check your math, Vibe.
是三人对六人
It's three against six.
但是我恐怕并不需要用尽全力来对付你们
Though I doubt I'll need to use all of my powers against you.
离我远点
You stay away from me!
你刚刚伤到迪沃了
You just hurt DeVoe.
迪沃是谁
Who the hell's DeVoe?
所以你们告诉我  这个想要杀我的三英尺高小妞
So you're telling me that this three foot tall chick
其实就是克利福德·迪沃吗
that tried to kill me is actually this Clifford DeVoe?
没错  如假包换
Oh, yeah. 100% dude.
迪沃在把他的意识
DeVoe is transferring his consciousness
转移至公车上所有人的身体里
to the other bodies of all the other people
并且获取他们的超能力
who were on the bus and got their powers with you.
等等  这个小女孩想要我的身体吗
Wait, this-- this little girl wants my body?
所以我们才想要保护你
That's why we're trying to protect you.
迪沃的大部分目标已经得手了
DeVoe's already taken most of his targets.
受害者
不  这是不可能的  现在不行
No, this ain't happening. Not now.
我最近才获得我的超能力
I only got my powers recently.
而现在我就像和音乐有了更深层次的联系
And now it's like I've got a deeper connection
那是我从未有过的
to my music than I've ever had.
我准备要录制我剩下的新专辑
I'm about to record the rest of my new album.
-准备开巡演  -伊兹  专辑可以等
- I'm about to go on tour-- - Izzy, your album can wait.
这个威胁可是真的
This threat is real.
我要打破记录也是真的
So is my big break.
你知不知道我为此付出了多大的努力吗
Do you have any idea how hard I've had to work for this?
我离开了家
I left my home.
我失去了朋友和好伙伴
I lost friends and good men,
我所容忍的烂事你都想像不到
and I have put up with more crap than you could imagine
这都是为了有一天我能完成梦想
so that one day I would get my dream.
现在你告诉我一个微型神经病
And now you're telling me that some pint-sized lunatic
要把这一切都夺走
is just gonna take it all away?
这就是为什么我们想让你留在
Which is exactly why we want you to stay here
-尖端科研实验室  -为什么
- at S.T.A.R. Labs. - Why?
你们难道会保护我什么的吗
Are y'all gonna protect me or something?
我们会训练你
We're gonna train you.
是吗
We are?
各位  她的能力可以削弱迪沃
Guys, her powers weakened DeVoe.
伊兹  这就意味着你最有可能阻止他
Izzy, that makes you our best shot at stopping him.
不行不行  这要求的太多了
No, no, this-this is all too much.
我都不知道你们是谁
I don't even know who you people are.
咱们没时间耗了
We don't have time for this.
闪电侠
Flash!
你是之前那个人
You're that guy from before.
是的  巴里·艾伦
Yeah, Barry Allen.
你也是  对不对
And so are you, aren't you?
没错  拉尔夫
Yeah. Ralph.
拉尔夫·德比
Ralph Dibny.
我是  西斯科  西斯科·拉蒙
I'm, uh, Cisco. Cisco Ramon.
-很高兴见到你  -好了  谢谢
- It's nice to meet you. - Okay, thank you.
你看  我不需要训练
Look, look, I-I don't need training.
尤其是你们的
Especially from you.
我只想要我的生活回来
All I need is my life back.
我不知道  各位
I don't know, guys.
我感觉如果我跟着她走进那走廊
I kinda feel like if I just followed her into that hallway
然后给她一通那种"你看"类型的
and just gave her one of those "Hey, look,"
激励谈话  没准能让她留下来
inspirational talks, I could probably get her to stay.
那你还在这里做什么呢
Then what are you still doing here?
抱歉  我不知道你们是不是
Sorry, I don't know if you, like,
要为这种事抽个签什么的
drew straws for this stuff or something.
-不会  快去  -好吧
- No, go! - Okay.
如果我是你就会小心点
I'd watch out if I were you.
有时候那里会走出机器人杀手
Sometimes killer robots come out of there.
继续走你的路  弹性人
Keep walking, Stretch.
我不想在黑暗的走廊里
I don't talk to creeps in dark hallways
和穿着紫色皮衣的怪人谈话
dressed in purple leather.
这个实际上更接近淡紫色
It's actually, uh, more of a mauve.
还有  我不是怪人
And, uh, I'm not a creep.
你看  伊兹  我知道你的感受
Look, Izzy, I know how you're feeling.
你获得能力的那一天
That day that you got your powers,
我也在同一辆巴士上
I was on the same bus.
所以那邪恶的花栗鼠  她也想杀了我
So that evil chipmunk, she wants to kill me, too.
求你
Please.
我觉得我应该会记得在巴士上见过你
I think I'd remember seeing you on my bus.
其实我那时候有些  大肚子
Actually I was kind of, uh, big boned back then.
我严格禁用杜松子酒  甜甜圈和悔过
I was on a strict diet of gin, donuts, and regret.
但是我有了另一次机会
But I got another shot at it.
于是我夹紧屁股不断努力
And I worked my tight butt off.
现在我是城里最性感的超级英雄
And now I'm the hottest superhero in town.
得了吧
Please.
我的生活  从没有这么好过
My life, it's never been better.
有点像是你的
Kinda like yours.
但你不怕失去一切吗
Yeah, but aren't you afraid of losing it all?
是  我怕
Yeah, I am.
所以我才成为这队伍的一员
Which is why I'm a part of this team.
你说你的家人舍弃了你
You said that your family bailed on you,
所以我明白你为什么不相信任何人
so I can understand why you wouldn't trust someone
能够照料你  但是  伊兹
to look out for you, but, Izzy,
我以当事人的身份告诉你  那些怪家伙
I can tell you firsthand that these amazing weirdoes,
他们绝不会舍弃你
they won't bail.
他们为我创造了一个伙伴系统
They created a buddy system for me.
如果你留下
And if you'll stay,
他们会保障你的安全
they'll keep you safe.
我保证
I promise.
那么  谁来当我的伙伴
So? Who's gonna be my buddy, then?
我可能得动用些关系
I may have to pull some strings,
但是我会看看我空不空闲
but I will see if I am available.
九号实验体的音波能力
Subject nine's sonic powers
加快了你内部器官的退化速度
accelerated the deterioration of your internal organs.
她不过是破坏了我的心房扑动和心跳过缓
She merely disrupted my atrial flutter and bradycardia.
这个身体反正也快被耗完了
This body is nearly drained anyway.
这缓解完全是浪费时间
Its palliation is a waste of time.
我需要那些生物识别器来诊断你的疾病
I need these biometric scans to fully assess your ailments.
那你应该把这个造的更有效率
Then you should have built this to work faster.
我已经尽力了
I'm doing all I can.
而你的成果却完全相反
Yet you achieved precisely the opposite.
我不能就这么站在一旁看着你受伤
I couldn't idly stand by and watch you be injured.
你的计划在失败
Your plan was failing.
有没有可能是不断的转换
Is it possible that the repeated transference
影响了你的认知能力
has affected your cognitive functioning?
我的脑子一点问题也没有
There is nothing wrong with my mind.
下一次我会保持冷静
Next time I will keep a level head.
伊兹  这个能帮助你集中能力
Izzy, this will help focus your powers.
可能在战斗中没什么帮助
Well, this ain't much help in a fight,
除非你是在和魔鬼决斗
unless you're dueling the devil.
别把它想成是一件武器
Don't think of it like a weapon.
就是做你一直想要做的事
Just do what you've always been dreaming to do.
创造属于你的声音
Make your own sound.
你是我的新目标吗  弹性人
Are you my new target, Stretch?
是啊  因为我没那么容易被破坏
Yeah, 'cause I don't break so easy.
得了吧
Please.
你脆弱得像个小树枝
You're built like a twig.
塞西尔·霍尔顿地检官
DA Cecille Horton.
你看起来很疲劳
You look tired.
是啊  因为我确实很疲劳
Yeah, that's 'cause I am tired.
这东西  没有作用
This thing, it doesn't work.
它肯定有  因为是我造的
It works because I built it.
还有你过度简化称呼的这个东西
And this thing, as you so ineloquently put it,
是一个内心活动缓冲器
happens to be a mental activity dampener
由九斤的小脑防护
that is ten pounds of cerebellum proof
反心灵感应索曼尼铁组成
anti-telepathy somani steel.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
对  问题就在这里
Yeah, that's the problem.
这个是  九斤重的东西
It is--It's ten pounds of that stuff.
所以呢
So?
天  好吧
Oh, gee- Okay.
然后呢
And?
我没法这样睡觉  哈里
I can't sleep like this, Harry.
这个在你看来会舒服吗
Does this look comfortable to you?
我想我是...  在我竭尽全力
I guess I was- While I was pulling
搞出超尖端的科技
state of the art technology out of my ass
来帮助解决你的问题时
to help you with your problem,
我忘了要让你感到舒服了
I forgot to make things comfortable for you.
你跟我说什么舒适度
Are you kidding me with comfortable?
你知道我还忘了什么吗
You know what else I forgot?
我想我还忘了  在我在想出
I guess I also forgot while I was coming up
新一代科技突破
with a generational breakthrough--
还有震动脑电波理论时
And vibrational brainwave theory,
我是在给豌豆公主做事
that I was working for the Princess and the Pea.
停下  停
Stop it! Stop!
放下来
Put it down.
哈里
Harry?
放下来
Put it down.
好吧  就...
Oh, okay. Just--
你这是怎么了
What the hell is wrong with you?
我很受挫
I'm frustrated.
-你受挫了  -是的
- You're frustrated? - Yes.
你开始冲我喊叫还扔东西
You start yelling at me and throwing things?
就好像你所有糟糕的想法
It is like every awful thought that you have,
完全不经过滤的从你口中涌出
it just comes pouring out of your mouth totally unfiltered.
我都不明...
I don't even under--
你平常的表现都这样吗
Is this normal behavior for you?
有时候这样
Sometimes behavior.
好吧  如果我想听一个成年人
Okay. If I wanna hear a grown man
像孩子一样尖叫
scream like a child,
我可以回家听乔因为压力做的关于
I will go home and listen to Joe's stress dreams
裸体出现在数学课上的梦
about showing up naked to math class.
这个...
Just...
拿着你的东西  哈里
Take your thing, Harry.
-再见  -真是挺重
- See you later. - It's heavy.
六小时之后
你又打偏了
You missed. Again.
你想怎么样  拉尔夫
Well, what do you expect, Ralph?
我已经练一整天了
I've been doing this all day.
我需要喝口水
I need a water break.
也许我们今天应该到此为止
Maybe we should call it a night.
还不行
Not yet.
他基本就没打中过拉尔夫
She's barely landed another shot on Ralph.
她需要更多的时间  巴仔
She needs more time, Bare.
她独自抵抗住了迪沃
She held her own against DeVoe.
完全是在原始本能下
Totally on raw instinct.
新手的运气吗
Beginner's luck?
我是说  拉尔夫可是训练了好几个月
I mean, it took months to train Ralph.
我们没有好几个月的时间
We don't have months.
这是我们第一次能够超前的机会
Look, this is our chance to get ahead for once.
如果迪沃再次出现
If DeVoe shows up again...
我们需要准备好
We have to be ready.
好了  拉尔夫  我来接手
All right, Ralph, I'm taking over.
谢了  巴仔  我们这里进展挺好的
Thanks, Bare, but we kinda got this covered over here and...
得逼她一下  拉尔夫
Gotta push her, Ralph.
好了  伊兹  我想看你能不能打中移动目标
All right, Izzy, I wanna see if you can hit a moving target.
-好  -你准备好了吗
- Okay. - You ready?
很好
Nice.
再加大一点难度
Take it up a few notches.
巴里
Barry!
伊兹怎么样
How's Izzy?
她只是需要缝几针  会没事的
She just needs a couple stitches, but she'll be okay.
拉尔夫不想离开她身边
Ralph won't leave her side.
我觉得他可能真的喜欢她
I think he might really like her.
拉尔夫不应该打扰她
Ralph shouldn't be bothering her at all.
她得注意力集中
I mean, she needs to stay focused.
伊兹虽然可能很好强  但是
Izzy might be scrappy, but, you know,
这是她第一天训练已经获得一阵子的超能力
it's her first day training with powers she's had for a little while.
我知道
I know.
巴里  你不觉得对她有点严苛吗
Barry, don't you think you're being a little hard on her?
不  我在试着训练她保护自己
No, I'm trying to teach her how to protect herself.
不  看上去你想让她成为英雄
No, it seems like you're trying to turn her into a hero.
而那条路并不适合所有人  巴里
And that path just isn't meant for everyone, Barry.
伊兹只是想要尽可能活下去
I mean, Izzy's just trying to survive.
我不逼她  她做不到的
Well, she's not going to if I don't push her.
你觉得这是和迪沃斗争的唯一办法吗
You think this is the only way to fight DeVoe?
不只是关于这个
It's not just about that.
爱瑞丝  你没在铁山监狱待过
Iris, you weren't at Iron Heights.
我亲眼目睹迪沃对贝姬的所作所为
I saw up close what DeVoe did to Becky.
对他们所有人  他们
To all of them. They--
而我什么都做不了
And I--I couldn't do anything
只能眼睁睁看一切发生
except just stand and watch it happen.
迪沃很残忍
DeVoe is ruthless.
他不会停手的  直到夺走她的超能力和生命
He's not gonna stop until he's taken her powers and her life.
他对她不会手软的  所以我也不能
He's not gonna go easy on her, so neither can I.
你不得不经历这一切  我很心疼
I am so sorry that you had to experience that.
但巴里  我们不能和迪沃一样无情
But Barry, we can't be ruthless like DeVoe.
他甘于牺牲所有人  一切
He's willing to sacrifice anyone and anything.
下次你逼她太过的时候记得这点  好吗
Just remember that the next time you're pushing too hard, okay?
你应该最明白英雄不是一夜之间练就的
You of all people know that heroes aren't made overnight.
乔不在
Joe's not here.
我不是来找乔的
Well, I don't wanna talk to Joe.
我觉得在我们最后一次谈话之后
I kind of figured after our last conversation
你应该再不想和我说话了
you would never wanna speak to me again.
你知道我可以读出你想法的吧
You do know I can hear your thoughts, right?
知道
Right.
不  哈里  我不打算再朝你大吼
No, Harry, I'm not gonna yell at you again.
-拜托  -那就好
- Just-- - All right, good.
给
Here.
-这是...  -内心活动缓冲器
- That's the-- - Mental activity dampener.
抱歉版本二号
Sorry version 2.0.
戴在你的眉骨上
Just adhere it to your supraobital ridge.
你就读不了韦斯特的心思了
You'll block West out.
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about...
最近  我好像无法阻止迪沃
You know, I just recently can't seem to stop DeVoe,
无法让我女儿杰西不恨我
can't stop my daughter Jessie from hating me,
在和同龄人交朋友时
can't seem to stop blowing it when I'm trying to befriend
也总是搞砸
someone who's my own age.
你是不是说交朋友了
Did you just say befriend?
这是你一直尝试的吗
That's what you've been trying to do?
你在尝试和我交朋友吗
You've been trying to befriend me?
是的  通过身边的人
Well, yes, through transitive property.
我尊敬韦斯特  韦斯特尊敬你  所以
I respect West, West respects you, so--
哈里  这真是太甜了
Harry, that was borderline sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们聊聊吧
Okay, well, let's talk.
什么时候
When?
-现在  -好的
- Now. - Okay.
好
Okay.
-我不是很  -来  哈里
- I'm not much-- - Come on, Harry.
好
Okay.
你想聊什么
What do you wanna talk about?
我先说吧
Oh, okay. I'll start.
你想告诉我这个的原理吗
you wanna tell me how this thing works?
是把乔的脑电波屏蔽了吗
Like, does it--does it keep Joe's brainwaves blocked out?
还是让我的读心波锁定了
Does it keep my mind reading waves locked in?
大多数情况是干扰接收的大脑活动
It mostly disrupts inbound brain activity,
但我觉得实际上
but I suppose actually
如果你要颠倒两极
if you were to reverse the polarity--
那才是有趣的
that is interesting.
-而且  -太棒了
- Also. - Yes.
哈里  你得这么做
Harry, you have to do that.
-是的  -现在
- Right. - Right now.
-聊天愉快  -是啊
- Okay, good chat. - Yeah.
太棒了
Okay.
应该没问题了
Should be good to go.
但可能会留点疤
Might be a little scar, though.
也不是第一次了  医生
Wouldn't be my first, doc.
可能也不是最后一次
Probably won't be my last.
会是的  如果这事我得担责任
It will be, if I have anything to do with it.
你为什么要担责任
Why would you have anything to do with it?
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
你在干什么
Wh--What are you doing?
以我来看  我在这里受的伤
The way I see it, I've gotten more hurt here
比和迪沃战斗受的更多
than I ever did fighting DeVoe,
所以我不会接受第二次训练了
so I'm not going to spend another second training.
这真是个坏主意
Okay, that is a really bad idea.
我已经打伤过迪沃了
I've already hurt DeVoe.
而且只是我孤身一人
By myself, without y'all.
我可以再来一次
I can do it again.
伊兹  对你而言唯一安全的选择
Izzy, the only way for you to stay safe is for you
就是和我们在一起
to stay with us.
我们是一个伙伴团体
It's the buddy system, right?
你不是我的伙伴  拉尔夫
You're not my buddy, Ralph.
别这样
Don't do this.
抱歉  拉尔夫
Sorry, Ralphie.
最初我预想了内心活动缓冲器
Initially I envisioned the mental activity dampener
只是作为干扰接收的脑电波的广播
as just disrupting inbound brainwave broadcasts,
但我和地检官塞西尔·霍尔顿聊了聊
but I talked to DA Cecile Horton
我们有了主意  颠倒两极  让仪器
and we had the idea to invert the polarity allowing this
还能够干扰向外的脑电波的广播
to disrupt outbound brainwave broadcasts as well.
-所以我们  -我们可以用这点对抗迪沃
- So we-- - We could use this against DeVoe.
我们可以用这点对抗迪沃
We could use this against DeVoe.
太天才了
That's brilliant.
我入伙了
I'm totally on board.
只是  名字是内心活动缓冲器吗
Except... mental activity dampener?
拉蒙  这名字是很烂
Ramon, the name's no good.
所以  重要时刻来了  拜托
Which is why-- drum roll, please--
我已经决定重命名为大脑抑制器
I have decided to rename this the cerebral inhibitor.
这就是我们研究出对抗迪沃的
This is where we came up with the cerebral inhibitor
大脑抑制器的地方
to use against DeVoe.
怎么了  你们这什么反应
What's that? What are you guys doing?
这表情什么意思
What are--What are those faces?
萨维塔到这里的时候
When Savitar came to S.T.A.R. Labs,
他说过我们会建一个装置对抗迪沃
he said we would build a device to use against DeVoe.
大脑抑制器
The cerebral inhibitor.
希望早点知道  我可是花了很久
I wish I had known that before I spent all this time
才想到这第二个名字
trying to come up with the second name.
起名很难
Naming is hard.
好  那我们可以把这个用于迪沃
Okay, so we can use this on DeVoe
阻止他把自己的意识寄居在
to keep him from projecting his consciousness
-新的肉体上  -没错
- into new bodies. - Precisely.
这怎么用
How does it work?
只要固定在他的前额就行
Just affix it to his forehead.
自己就激活  就这么简单
It activates. Simple as that.
我会做一些调整  你们可以用了
I'll make a few adjustments, you'll be good to go.
好
All right.
哈里搞定后  我们去找迪沃
Okay, when Harry's done, we go after DeVoe.
我们有了伊兹的超能力  大脑抑制器
I mean, we have Izzy's powers, the cerebral inhibitor--
我们有了阻止他的一切
I mean, we have everything that we need to stop him.
现在不行了
Except that we don't.
伊兹走了
Izzy's gone.
什么  发生了什么
What? What happened?
你和她说了什么
What did you say to her?
-我  -对
- Me? - Yeah.
菜鸟  她是因为你上路的
Rookie, Homeslice hit the road because of you.
她自以为能单枪匹马对抗迪沃
She's convinced she can take on DeVoe by herself.
她走就是为了这事
That's what she's gone to do.
你总是逼她
You kept pushing and pushing her.
现在把她逼走了
Pushed her right out the door, man.
这不公平
Okay, that's not fair.
他没说错
No, it's all right.
是我逼她太过了
I did, I pushed her too hard.
她走是我的错
It's my fault that she's out there.
但如果迪沃赶在我们之前找到她
But if DeVoe gets to her before we do--
千万不能
That cannot happen.
西斯科  你得用超能力感应一下她在哪里
Cisco, you need to use your ESPN and find out where she is.
给我这东西
Give me that thing.
金发妞
Hey, blondie!
想要麻烦吗  我来了
You want trouble? Here I am.
好啊
Well!
看看谁最后决定露出那副丧表情了
Look who finally decided to show her sorry face.
没人喜欢偷窥者
Nobody likes a peeping Tom.
拜拜  拉蒙先生
Good-bye, Mr. Ramon.
西斯科  你还好吗  能听到我吗
Cisco, are you okay? Can you hear me?
她在仓库区域
She's at the warehouse district.
迪沃在那
DeVoe's there.
我不能和你们一起
I can't go with you guys.
我得照顾西斯科
I gotta take care of Cisco.
好  拉尔夫  只有我们两个了
All right, Ralph, it's just me and you.
来吧
Come on.
勇士啊  鲍温女士
Bravo, Ms. Bowin.
在我所有研究对像中
Of all my subjects,
你是唯一一个可抵御我的
you're the only one to mount a credible defense against me.
亲爱的  你话太多了
Darlin', you talk too much.
时不时会有点像这样的坏运气
A modicum of bad luck at a time like this.
不幸啊
How unfortunate.
你小提琴拉的不错
You're quite the fiddler.
提琴手  拉蒙先生可能会这么叫你
The fiddler, Mr. Ramon might say,
搞定这事  赢了它
nailed it and won.
拉尔夫  你来找我了
Ralph? You came after me.
我们都来了
We all did.
拉尔夫  我拖住迪沃
Hey, Ralph, I'll keep DeVoe busy.
你给他戴上抑制器
You just get the inhibitor on.
你好  艾伦先生
Hello, Mr. Allen.
迪沃  你得不到她的
DeVoe, you're not getting her.
闪电侠
Flash!
可怜的多米尼克
Poor Dominic.
他不知道他在读心的同时还能影响他们
He didn't know he could affect minds as well as read them.
现在我让你明白脑动脉瘤是什么感受了
Now I've taught you what a brain aneurysm feels like.
快离开
Get out of here.
该死
Ah, crap!
谢谢你  伦丁先生
Thank you, Mr. Rundine.
让你知道知道招惹乡村女孩的后果
That'll teach you to mess with a country girl.
大脑抑制器接入
Cerebral inhibitor's attached.
起作用了吗
Is it working?
起作用了
Oh, it's working.
迪肯先生怎么说的
How did Mr. Deacon put it?
对了
Ah, yes.
叫我基尔戈
Call me Kilgore.
怎么回事
The hell?
她是黑了抑制器吗
Did she hack the inhibitor?
不不不  这不可能
No, no, no, that's impossible.
那里面有关断连接的芯片
There's a kill switch microchip
能够阻止插入码连接网络
that prevents the patch from networking.
我听得到你的无线信号  威尔斯先生
I can hear your radio signal, Mr. Wells.
以前你对我说  我没有自己以为的那么聪明
You told me once I wasn't as smart as I thought.
你又错了
Wrong again.
伊兹
Izzy!
拉尔夫
Ralph?
带她离开
Get her out of there!
拉尔夫  我们做不到
Ralph, we can't.
带她离开
Get her out!
我们做不到
We can't.
伊兹  看着我就好
Izzy, just look at me.
伊兹
Izzy!
看着我  坚持住
Keep looking at me!
好多了
Much better.
请通知拉蒙先生
please inform Mr. Ramon that,
虽然我不需要六种能力
while I had no need for all six of my powers,
现在我有第七种了
I now have a seventh.
恐怕这周末我跟我老婆有的忙了
I'm afraid I'm gonna be busy with my wife this weekend,
小拉尔夫
Ralphie.
不
No.
-拉尔夫怎么样  -不是很好
- How's Ralph? - Not great.
这事不该发生的
This shouldn't have happened.
迪沃本不该逃出生天的
DeVoe wasn't supposed to walk away from this.
可是他逃掉了
Yeah, well, he did.
-因为我  -我们都尽力保护她了
- Because of me. - We all tried to protect her.
是我造的抑制器  斯诺
I built the inhibitor, Snow.
它出了问题  就是我的错
If it failed, it's my fault.
而我连原因都不知道
And I don't even know why.
或许我高估了微型燃烧的基础结构
Maybe I overestimated the micro-combustion infrastructure,
又或许是我低估了
or maybe I underestimated
每个突触路由器之间的用时  或者...
the amount of time between each synapse router, or--
也许抑制器并没有出问题
Maybe it didn't malfunction at all.
各位  是萨维塔说我们应该用
Guys, Savitar said that we would use
大脑抑制器对付迪沃的
the cerebral inhibitor against DeVoe.
对  可他没说这会有用
Yeah, he didn't say it was gonna work.
是  抑制器没起作用
Yeah, well, it didn't work.
是因为...
'Cause...
我不够聪明  做不出有用的抑制器
I'm not smart enough to make it work.
哈里
Harry!
-你要去哪儿  -出去
- Where are you going? - Out.
各位  我们必须再一次找出迪沃
Guys, we have to find DeVoe again.
怎么找
How?
西斯科在震波状态下追踪迪沃
Cisco tracked down DeVoe in his Vibe state,
结果差点送了命
and he almost got himself killed.
事实上...
Actually...
我们可能有别的方法来定位他
We might have a different way of pinpointing him.
看看这个
Check this out.
宇宙  最终的疆域
Space. The final frontier.
现在你看得到...
Now you see it...
现在又看不到了
Now you don't.
迪沃消失的时候
That's exactly what it looks like
看起来就是这样的
when DeVoe disappears.
这是有人进入口袋维度时
That is the warping signature of someone moving
会出现的曲波
into a pocket dimension.
有人愿意解释一下这什么意思吗
Does someone wanna explain what that means?
爱因斯坦假定  在理论上
Einstein postulated that it was theoretically possible
时空内特定区域的折叠是有可能
for a region-specific fold in the space time to exist
存在于我们通常所认为的四维空间中的
between the four dimensions that we typically think of.
跟没解释一样
Yeah, that doesn't help.
这是...
It's-- -
是另一个维度
It's another dimension.
在这个维度你可以随意进出世界上的任一地点
One that you can enter or exit at any location in the world.
就好像迪沃在那条小路上抓到了我
Like how DeVoe captured me in that alley
然后又把我带到了城市上空某处现身
but then he brought me back out to somewhere above the city.
你是在说迪沃的贼窝是在口袋维度里吗
Are you saying that DeVoe's lair is in a pocket dimension?
西斯科  你真棒
Cisco, this is great.
我们能追踪到他吗
Can we track him?
这个我还在想办法
That I'm, uh, still working on.
那就快点想
Okay, work faster.
你尽力就好  好吗  我们来把他揪出来
Just do your best, all right? Let's find him.
-好  -我去看看拉尔夫
- All right. - I'm gonna go check on Ralph.
好的
All right.
你说得对
You were right.
就算我再想抓住迪沃  让生活回归正轨
As much as I wanna get DeVoe, get back to our lives,
我也不能急
I can't rush this.
对极速者来说这有点难啊
It's gonna be a little hard for a speedster.
对失业的极速者来说尤其难
Especially an unemployed speedster.
别担心  你会有所发现的
Don't worry. You're gonna find something.
在这之前呢
And until then?
不如先亲亲你老婆
You can start by kissing your wife.
你看着挺忙啊
Someone looks busy.
是  有点工作要做
Yep, just a little bit of work.
不如你先...
Why don't you have a--
好吧
Okay.
-哈里  -你说
- Harry. - Yes?
-我想谢谢你  -谢我什么
- I wanted to say thank you. - For what?
麦德2.0  运行起来简直完美
The MAD 2.0. It works like a charm.
我休息得很好
I am rested.
要是你能对我因怀孕
If you could just do something
而浮肿的脚踝做些什么就更好了
about these swollen pregnant ankles of mine--
我觉得浮肿很正常
I think that's a normal thing.
你喝了不少水
You drink lots of water.
坐下的时候不要跷二郎腿
Don't cross your legs when you sit.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
谢谢你的建议
Thank you for the info.
举手之劳而已  毕竟...
Least I could do after all the--
我有发脾气的坏毛病
Rage. I have a problem with rage.
显然我一犯错就容易犯这个毛病
Apparently it tends to crop up when I make mistakes.
当个人类确实不易
Makes it tough to be human.
人类是个难缠的物种
Well, humans are a tricky species.
不管怎样  我道歉
Anyway, I apologize.
我接受
Apology accepted.
你只是需要有个人来说说话
You just needed somebody to talk to.
是啊  我...
Yeah, well, I--
你是在读我的想法吗
Are you doing that thing where you're reading my mind?
你在读我的想法是不是
You're reading my mind, aren't you?
或许吧  对  我读了
Maybe. Yeah, yeah, I am.
你应该打电话给她  哈里
You should call her, Harry.
杰西在另一个星球上  塞西尔·霍尔顿地检官
Jessie's on a different planet, DA Cecile Horton.
但这个问题不会自己消失的
But this problem isn't gonna just go away.
要是她...
What if she--
要是她没来呢
What if she doesn't come?
你不邀请她就永远不会知道
You're not gonna know unless you invite her.
太美妙了
That was beautiful.
也是个令人欣喜的变化  从前我们的身体
And a welcome change from the derivative pabulum
会抑制我们吸收这种衍生的精神食粮
this body subjected us to before.
我们的计划重回正轨了
Our plan is back on schedule.
确实如此
Indeed it is.
要定位的目标没几个了
Only a few more subjects left to locate.
拉尔夫·德比  私家侦探
哥们
Hey, man.
要是不方便我可以一会儿再来
I can come back if--
没有  没事的
No, it's--it's okay.
听着...
Look, um...
要是你需要离队一段时间  我完全理解
I totally understand if you need some time away from the team.
眼睁睁的看着一个人失去
I mean, to lose someone right in front of you...
还是你在乎的那个人
Especially someone you care about...
伊兹是与众不同的
Izzy was very special.
确实
She was.
但  但现在...
But--But now...
迪沃依然逍遥法外
DeVoe's still out there.
在这个威胁解除之前
And until that threat's over...
我们还得保持这个伙伴关系
We gotta keep this buddy system going.
我想到你会这么说了  艾伦
I thought you might say that, Allen.
所以我给你准备了这个
Which is why I got you this.
巴里·艾伦  私家侦探
你想让我做你的搭档吗
You want me to be your partner?
你快得了吧
Oh, hey, come on.
我这神探才用不上帮手呢
This, uh, this Turner don't need no Hooch.
不过...
But...
我确实明白一条法律未犯
I do know what it's like to get fired from CCPD
就被中城警局开除是什么感觉
when you didn't even really break the law.
你铁定是犯法了
You absolutely broke the law.
我还记得  我丢了工作后
And I remember after I lost my job,
感觉我一部分的人格都丧失了
felt like I lost a piece of my identity.
现在你不用烦心这个问题了
And now you won't have to deal with that problem.
下次我们出外勤的时候
So the next time we're out in the field
要是有人问你为谁卖命
and somebody asks you who you work for,
你就不用再支支吾吾的了
you won't have to get all stammery.
你喜欢我
You like me.
你真的很喜欢我
You really like me.
别对我这么温柔  菜鸟
Don't go getting all soft on me now, rookie.
你和我  我们得站起来
You and I, we gotta stand up,
予以反击
and we gotta fight back.
正如伊兹所希望的那样
Just like Izzy would have wanted.
没错
That's right.
世上还有三个人需要我们的帮助
There's three more people out there who need our help,
我们得在迪沃之前找到他们
and we need to find them before DeVoe does.
等我们找到他们后
And after we do that...
我要打倒迪沃
I'm gonna take DeVoe down.